

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211







Associate IT Business Analyst seeking roles in IT Project Management, Gap Analysis, IT Infrastructure Management, Business Analysis, Business Analytics, Business Development, Process Improvement, Product Development, Customer Success and Presales.



Current Designation: Business Analyst

Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 3 Month(s)

Current Company: Globant

Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Mechanical]

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad, Pune

Role: Business Analyst

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Gap Analysis, IT Infrastructure Management, Business Analysis, Business Analytics, Business Development, Process Improvement, Product Development, Agile Methodology, Customer Success, Presales

Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 5-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Business Analysis:- 3 plus years of experience in elicitation of requirements from clients thereby delivering effective and appropriate solutions mostly within fixed deadlines. Documented requirements with mockups and workflows for easier understandings.

Customer Success:-Experienced in client relationship management, resolving conflicts and clearing roadblocks thereby being able to convince clients for more opportunities and hence reducing Customer churn.

Presales:- Supported Business Development with engaging Product Demo's. Helped in onboarding clients through quality product demo's and Proof of Concepts. Gained insights about RFP, SOW etc.

Customer Service: - Occasional end user or customer support

Process Experience:- ITSM(ITIL), BPM

Domain Experience:-

Automobile Manufacturing and Pharmaceutical:- 21 CFR Part 11, CSV, GAMP 5, etc

Work Experience

Globant as Business Analyst Dec 2020 to Till Date

Servicenow Modules Implementation - Business Analyst

Ample Logic as BPM-Low Code Business Analyst Aug 2020 to Dec 2020

Helped Sales Team to onboard Clients by providing Proof of Concepts and conducting Client Demos.

Worked with the low code development platform, which delivers flawless pharma and other software applications with seamless user/customer experience

Implemented E Log books for various pharma clients thereby successfully converting their paper logs into E-logs.

Created necessary prototypes, constructed process workflows thereby eventually developing the Elog Book using the low code platform

Reached out to developers only for complex customizations.

Created RTM and test case document

Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Worked on BRD, FRD, Configuration Specification and Risk Assessment Documents.

Models:-V, Waterfall Agile.

Domain Knowledge:- Basic knowledge on Concepts like GAMP 5, 21 CFR Part 11, FDA, EU GMP Annex 11, CSV, SAP Integration.

Cognizant Technology Solutions India Ltd as ITSM-Service Now Business Analyst Aug 2017 to Jun 2020

ITSMConsultant:-Facilitated workshops with clients to gather future state processes for Incident Management, Change Management, and Catalog Management using Service Now.

Vendor and Change Management:-Effectively handled Vendor and Change Management activities in IT Infra Sector using Service Now.

Provided guidance to developers and quality assurance testers thereby clearing their doubts.

IT Infrastructure Business Analyst-Discussed with clients to understand Server Virtualization related requirements thereby providing necessary solution. Domain Knowledge:- ITIL , ITSM Basics.

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Mechanical) from Biju Patnaik University of Technology (BPUT) in 2016

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
JIRA basics			
VMWare Vsphere			
SQL , API integration			
ServiceNow			
Camunda BPM			
MS Visio			
Balsamiq			
HP Service Manager			
MS OFFICE			
ITSM, BPM, Change Management			

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Odiya				
Bengali				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.